<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Jordan Knightin</title><description>Insights on technology, finance, and travel - covering trends, smart investing, and top destinations to keep you informed and inspired.</description><link>https://alietech.github.io/</link><item><title>How to Reset a Smart Thermostat to Factory Settings?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-reset-a-smart-thermostat-to-factory-settings/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-reset-a-smart-thermostat-to-factory-settings/</guid><description>&quot;Learn step-by-step how to easily reset your smart thermostat to its factory settings. This comprehensive guide ensures a seamless reset process for various thermostat models, helping you troubleshoot issues or prepare for a fresh start.&quot;</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Much Electricity Does a Coffee Machine Use Per Hour?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-much-electricity-does-a-coffee-machine-use-per-hour/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-much-electricity-does-a-coffee-machine-use-per-hour/</guid><description>Discover the energy consumption of your coffee machine with our detailed guide on how much electricity it uses per hour. Make informed decisions to optimize energy use and reduce costs while enjoying your daily brew.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Make Iced Coffee Using a Coffee Machine in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-make-iced-coffee-using-a-coffee-machine-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-make-iced-coffee-using-a-coffee-machine-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Discover the ultimate guide to making the perfect iced coffee using a coffee machine in 2025. Elevate your coffee experience with modern techniques and tips for the freshest, most flavorful iced brew. Whether you&apos;re a beginner or a coffee enthusiast, this step-by-step guide will ensure your iced coffee is always refreshingly cool and delicious.&quot;</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Are Key Symbols in the Great Gatsby in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-key-symbols-in-the-great-gatsby-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-key-symbols-in-the-great-gatsby-in-2025/</guid><description>Unlock the timeless symbolism of &quot;The Great Gatsby&quot; in this 2025 analysis. Explore key symbols like the green light, the valley of ashes, and more to deepen your understanding of F. Scott Fitzgerald&apos;s classic novel. Perfect for students and literary enthusiasts alike.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Is Tensorflow and How Is It Used in Machine Learning?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-is-tensorflow-and-how-is-it-used-in-machine-learning/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-is-tensorflow-and-how-is-it-used-in-machine-learning/</guid><description>Discover the power of TensorFlow, a leading open-source platform for machine learning. Learn how TensorFlow simplifies the development of machine learning models with its versatile tools and libraries, and explore its applications across industries for building intelligent systems and enhancing data-driven decision-making. Perfect for beginners and experts looking to deepen their understanding of machine learning technologies.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Create a Podcast and Earn Money in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-create-a-podcast-and-earn-money-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-create-a-podcast-and-earn-money-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Discover the ultimate guide to launching a successful podcast in 2025 and learn effective strategies to monetize it. From initial setup and recording tips to leveraging modern monetization techniques, start earning from your podcast today!&quot;</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Are the Key Features Of Tensorflow 2.x in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-the-key-features-of-tensorflow-2-x-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-the-key-features-of-tensorflow-2-x-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Discover the pivotal features of TensorFlow 2.x in 2025, including advancements in ease of use, performance improvements, and integration capabilities. Stay ahead in AI development with insights into the newest updates and practical applications.&quot;</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Is the Best Way to Learn Tensorflow Online in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-is-the-best-way-to-learn-tensorflow-online-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-is-the-best-way-to-learn-tensorflow-online-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Discover the ultimate guide to mastering TensorFlow online in 2025. Explore top courses, resources, and expert tips to enhance your AI and machine learning skills efficiently and effectively. Stay ahead in the tech world with the best learning strategies!&quot;</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Install Tensorflow on Windows for Beginners?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-install-tensorflow-on-windows-for-beginners/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-install-tensorflow-on-windows-for-beginners/</guid><description>&quot;Discover a simple, step-by-step guide to installing TensorFlow on Windows. Perfect for beginners, this tutorial walks you through the process, ensuring a smooth setup for your machine learning projects.&quot;</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Are Easy Side Hustles to Make Money Fast in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-easy-side-hustles-to-make-money-fast-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-easy-side-hustles-to-make-money-fast-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Discover the best side hustles for 2025 to boost your income quickly and easily. Explore flexible opportunities that fit your lifestyle and start earning fast with these simple side gigs.&quot;</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Size Should an Indoor Sauna Be for a Small Home?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-size-should-an-indoor-sauna-be-for-a-small-home/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-size-should-an-indoor-sauna-be-for-a-small-home/</guid><description>&quot;Discover the ideal indoor sauna size for a small home with our comprehensive guide. Learn how to maximize comfort and efficiency in your limited space, ensuring a perfect balance of relaxation and practicality. Find out expert recommendations and tips for creating your personal retreat.&quot;</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Improve My Indoor Sauna Experience in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-improve-my-indoor-sauna-experience-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-improve-my-indoor-sauna-experience-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Discover the ultimate tips and latest innovations for enhancing your indoor sauna experience in 2025. From advanced technology to personalized wellness routines, transform your relaxation time into a luxurious escape. Read more for expert advice on optimizing climate control, incorporating aromatherapy, and upgrading sauna accessories to elevate your home spa.&quot;</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Are Php Data Types in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-php-data-types-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-php-data-types-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Explore the latest PHP data types in 2025 with our comprehensive guide. Understand the evolution of PHP types, their applications, and best practices to enhance your coding skills. Stay ahead in web development with the updated PHP knowledge you need!&quot;</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Are Typescript Generics and Why Use Them in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-typescript-generics-and-why-use-them-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-typescript-generics-and-why-use-them-in-2025/</guid><description>Unlock the future of coding with TypeScript generics in 2025! This comprehensive guide explores the power and versatility of generics, revealing why they are essential for writing robust, flexible, and scalable code. Discover how to enhance your TypeScript projects by leveraging generics for improved type safety and code reusability. Perfect for developers aiming to stay ahead in modern software development!</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Send an Email Using Php in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-send-an-email-using-php-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-send-an-email-using-php-in-2025/</guid><description>Learn how to send emails seamlessly using PHP in 2025 with our comprehensive guide. Discover the latest methods, best practices, and code examples to efficiently integrate email functionality into your PHP applications.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Did Board Games Evolve Over Time in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-did-board-games-evolve-over-time-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-did-board-games-evolve-over-time-in-2025/</guid><description>Explore the fascinating evolution of board games up to 2025, uncovering how technological advances, cultural shifts, and innovative game design have transformed this beloved pastime. Discover the latest trends and timeless classics in this comprehensive overview.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Do Board Games Improve Social Skills in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-do-board-games-improve-social-skills-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-do-board-games-improve-social-skills-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Discover how board games are set to enhance social skills in 2025, fostering communication, collaboration, and empathy. Explore the surprising benefits of playing board games in this insightful article for readers of all ages.&quot;</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Store Board Games Effectively in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-store-board-games-effectively-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-store-board-games-effectively-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Discover the best strategies for storing board games in 2025 with our comprehensive guide. Learn innovative tips and space-saving solutions to keep your collection organized, protected, and easily accessible for endless fun with family and friends.&quot;</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Are the Best Strategy Board Games for Beginners?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-the-best-strategy-board-games-for-beginners/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-the-best-strategy-board-games-for-beginners/</guid><description>Discover the top strategy board games perfect for beginners! Explore our curated list of easy-to-learn games that combine fun and strategy, ideal for kickstarting your board gaming journey.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Historical Board Games Are Worth Exploring in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-historical-board-games-are-worth-exploring-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-historical-board-games-are-worth-exploring-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Discover the top historical board games to explore in 2025, offering a blend of engaging strategy and rich storytelling. Dive into the past and enhance your game night with these timeless classics.&quot;</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Is the Best Ide for Golang Development in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-is-the-best-ide-for-golang-development-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-is-the-best-ide-for-golang-development-in-2025/</guid><description>Discover the top IDEs for Go development in 2025! Explore comprehensive comparisons and expert recommendations to find the best Integrated Development Environment that enhances your productivity and coding experience in Golang. Whether you&apos;re a beginner or an advanced developer, stay ahead with the ultimate tools for your Go programming projects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Bitcoin a Good Investment for Retirement Planning?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/is-bitcoin-a-good-investment-for-retirement-planning/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/is-bitcoin-a-good-investment-for-retirement-planning/</guid><description>Explore the potential of Bitcoin for retirement planning in our comprehensive article. Discover whether it&apos;s a viable investment option, assess its risks and rewards, and learn strategies to integrate this cryptocurrency into your retirement portfolio for long-term growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Use Context in Golang in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-use-context-in-golang-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-use-context-in-golang-in-2025/</guid><description>Discover the essential guide to using context in Go for 2025. Enhance your Go applications with best practices and advanced techniques for managing execution, deadlines, and cancellations effectively. Perfect for developers aiming to streamline their Golang projects with up-to-date context usage strategies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Non-stick Donut Makers Better Than Regular Ones?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/are-non-stick-donut-makers-better-than-regular-ones/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/are-non-stick-donut-makers-better-than-regular-ones/</guid><description>&quot;Explore the ultimate showdown: Non-stick vs. Regular Donut Makers. Discover which type is best for creating delicious, perfectly cooked donuts at home. Uncover the advantages and drawbacks of each to make the right choice for your kitchen needs.&quot;</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Much Does It Cost to Install a Permanent Pizza Oven?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-much-does-it-cost-to-install-a-permanent-pizza-oven/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-much-does-it-cost-to-install-a-permanent-pizza-oven/</guid><description>&quot;Discover the costs associated with installing a permanent pizza oven, including materials, labor, and maintenance. Our comprehensive guide breaks down expenses to help you plan your ideal outdoor or indoor culinary addition. Perfect for pizza enthusiasts and home improvement planners alike.&quot;</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Maintain and Clean a Pizza Oven Properly in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-maintain-and-clean-a-pizza-oven-properly-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-maintain-and-clean-a-pizza-oven-properly-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Discover expert tips for maintaining and cleaning your pizza oven in 2025. Ensure perfect performance and longevity with step-by-step guidance for both indoor and outdoor ovens. Keep your pizza oven spotless and efficient all year round!&quot;</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Use a Donut Maker for the First Time in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-use-a-donut-maker-for-the-first-time-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-use-a-donut-maker-for-the-first-time-in-2025/</guid><description>“Unlock the magic of homemade donuts with our step-by-step guide on using a donut maker for the first time in 2025. Discover tips for perfect results, easy recipes, and insider tricks to impress everyone with your baking skills.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Is the Best Lua Ide for Beginners in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-is-the-best-lua-ide-for-beginners-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-is-the-best-lua-ide-for-beginners-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Discover the best Lua IDE for beginners in 2025 with our comprehensive guide. Explore top-rated tools featuring user-friendly interfaces, advanced features, and seamless performance to kickstart your Lua programming journey.&quot;</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Create a Function in Lua in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-create-a-function-in-lua-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-create-a-function-in-lua-in-2025/</guid><description>Discover the ultimate guide on creating functions in Lua in 2025. Master the basics, explore advanced techniques, and enhance your programming skills with our step-by-step instructions. Perfect for beginners and seasoned developers alike.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Customize the Look and Feel Of Your Forum in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-customize-the-look-and-feel-of-your-forum-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-customize-the-look-and-feel-of-your-forum-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Unlock the full potential of your online community with our comprehensive 2025 guide on customizing your forum&apos;s look and feel. Discover the latest tools, trends, and techniques to create an engaging, user-friendly platform that stands out in today&apos;s digital landscape.&quot;</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Start a Forum Website From Scratch in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-start-a-forum-website-from-scratch-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-start-a-forum-website-from-scratch-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Learn how to effortlessly start a forum website from scratch in 2025 with our step-by-step guide. Discover the latest tools, tips, and strategies to build a thriving online community and foster engaging discussions.&quot;</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Are the Legal Considerations When Creating a Forum?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-the-legal-considerations-when-creating-a-forum/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-the-legal-considerations-when-creating-a-forum/</guid><description>&quot;Explore the essential legal considerations for creating a forum, including privacy policies, user agreements, copyright issues, and moderation practices, to ensure compliance and protect your online community.&quot;</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Are the Security Best Practices in Symfony in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-the-security-best-practices-in-symfony-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-the-security-best-practices-in-symfony-in-2025/</guid><description>Master Symfony security in 2025 with our comprehensive guide on best practices. Learn essential techniques to protect your applications from vulnerabilities and ensure robust security, from authentication to data encryption. Stay ahead in safeguarding your Symfony projects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Is Rate Limiting in Nginx and How to Implement It?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-is-rate-limiting-in-nginx-and-how-to-implement-it/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-is-rate-limiting-in-nginx-and-how-to-implement-it/</guid><description>&quot;Learn how to effectively implement rate limiting in NGINX with our comprehensive guide. Discover what rate limiting is, why it&apos;s essential for managing web traffic, and step-by-step instructions to enhance your server&apos;s performance and security. Perfect for web administrators aiming to optimize their NGINX configurations.&quot;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Redirect Http to Https in Nginx in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-redirect-http-to-https-in-nginx-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-redirect-http-to-https-in-nginx-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Discover the step-by-step guide to redirecting HTTP to HTTPS in Nginx for 2025. Enhance your website&apos;s security and SEO with our comprehensive tutorial, ensuring a seamless transition to a more secure web experience.&quot;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can Rowing Machines Build Muscle in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/can-rowing-machines-build-muscle-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/can-rowing-machines-build-muscle-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Discover how rowing machines can enhance muscle building in 2025. Explore the latest insights, benefits, and expert tips on maximizing your strength training with modern rowing technology.&quot;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Is Kotlin Different From Other Jvm Languages in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-is-kotlin-different-from-other-jvm-languages-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-is-kotlin-different-from-other-jvm-languages-in-2025/</guid><description>Discover the unique features of Kotlin that set it apart from other JVM languages in 2025. Explore its modern syntax, interoperability, and advanced capabilities that make it a standout choice for developers today.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Rowing Machine a Good Cardio Workout in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/is-rowing-machine-a-good-cardio-workout-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/is-rowing-machine-a-good-cardio-workout-in-2025/</guid><description>Unlock the full potential of your fitness routine in 2025 with rowing machines. Discover why rowing offers an unparalleled cardio workout that enhances endurance, torches calories, and strengthens muscles. Explore the benefits and insights on incorporating this dynamic exercise into your regimen.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Are Kotlin&apos;s Security Features in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-kotlin-s-security-features-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-kotlin-s-security-features-in-2025/</guid><description>Discover Kotlin&apos;s advanced security features in 2025, including robust encryption, secure coding practices, and enhanced threat detection. Learn how Kotlin&apos;s updates enhance app security and protect sensitive data in the evolving digital landscape.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Are Neoprene Dumbbells in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-neoprene-dumbbells-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-neoprene-dumbbells-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Discover the benefits and innovative features of neoprene dumbbells in 2025. Explore why these versatile, durable, and ergonomic weights are a must-have for fitness enthusiasts seeking style and functionality in their workout routines.&quot;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Are the Main Benefits Of Using Kotlin Over Java?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-the-main-benefits-of-using-kotlin-over-java/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-are-the-main-benefits-of-using-kotlin-over-java/</guid><description>Discover the advantages of using Kotlin over Java in your Android development projects. Learn how Kotlin enhances productivity, boosts code safety, and offers modern features, making it the preferred choice for developers. Explore the key benefits that set Kotlin apart from Java in this insightful guide.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Muscles Does a Rowing Machine Work in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-muscles-does-a-rowing-machine-work-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/what-muscles-does-a-rowing-machine-work-in-2025/</guid><description>&quot;Discover the comprehensive benefits of using a rowing machine in 2025. Explore how rowing targets key muscle groups including your arms, legs, core, and back, enhancing your strength and fitness. Unlock the secret to a full-body workout that promotes muscle growth and improved endurance.&quot;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Connect Php to a Mysql Database in 2025?</title><link>https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-connect-php-to-a-mysql-database-in-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alietech.github.io/blog/how-to-connect-php-to-a-mysql-database-in-2025/</guid><description>Learn the most up-to-date techniques for connecting PHP to MySQL databases in 2025. This comprehensive guide covers the latest best practices and code examples to ensure a secure and efficient connection for your web applications.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>